<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chiao-Yi Wu | The Clinical Brain Lab</title>
    <link>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/author/chiao-yi-wu/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/author/chiao-yi-wu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Chiao-Yi Wu</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/images/icon_hu30d0ad82a56c1708370149d7b9443316_148842_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Chiao-Yi Wu</title>
      <link>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/author/chiao-yi-wu/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Age-Related Changes in Episodic Processing of Scenes: A Functional Activation and Connectivity Study</title>
      <link>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/publication/2023_aging_sensors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/publication/2023_aging_sensors/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Dance to Maintain Cognitive Performance and Cortical Morphology in Older Adults with MCI</title>
      <link>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/publication/2022_ohbm_dancing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/publication/2022_ohbm_dancing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
neuroscience-informed remediation of reading difficulties for bilingual readers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ongoing projects:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective Biliteracy: The Impact of Script Sets on Bilingual Reading Networks for Typical and Atypical Readers - &lt;em&gt;funded by NTU-JHU Collaborative Grant&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Modulating Reading Networks -&lt;em&gt;funded by NTU-JHU Collaborative Grant&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cognitive Science of Multilingualism In Children (COSMIC) - &lt;em&gt;funded by National Research Foundation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promoting Effective Biliteracy</title>
      <link>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/project/pebbles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/project/pebbles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The project aims to develop an early screening and training programme to promote balanced bilingual development and biliteracy attainment in early childhood.
Using a multimodal approach, we will identify early neural, cognitive, and environmental predictors in preschool years for later bilingual and biliteracy development.
We will evaluate the neurocognitive effects of different training programmes on enhancing biliteracy development. The knowledge gained from the project will broaden our understanding of the neurocognitive development of language and reading networks in young bilinguals.
The findings will have significant implications for early screening and effective training for promoting balanced bilingual and biliteracy development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ongoing project:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Promoting Effective Biliteracy in Early Childhood: A Systematic Screening and Training Programme for Balanced Bilingual Development - &lt;em&gt;funded by Singapore Millennium Foundation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The role of regional heterogeneity in age-related differences in functional hemispheric asymmetry: an fMRI study</title>
      <link>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/publication/2018_ageing-asymmetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://clinicalbrainlab.github.io/publication/2018_ageing-asymmetry/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
